{
    "subject": "resource/Kirarin_Revolution",
    "predicate": "property/content",
    "object": "resource/Kirarin_Revolution",
    "human_readable": "The content of Kirarin Revolution is Kirarin Revolution.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9606872797012329,
            "question": "What is the content of Kirarin Revolution?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7820757031440735,
            "question": "Does Kirarin Revolution involve music or performing arts?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7772340774536133,
            "question": "What genre might Kirarin Revolution belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7591835856437683,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in Kirarin Revolution?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7536855936050415,
            "question": "What is the target audience for Kirarin Revolution?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7440447807312012,
            "question": "Is Kirarin Revolution a fictional story?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7253479361534119,
            "question": "Where can one find more information about Kirarin Revolution?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7250319719314575,
            "question": "Are there any popular characters in Kirarin Revolution?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6535288095474243,
            "question": "Could Kirarin Revolution be a television show?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.648149847984314,
            "question": "Has Kirarin Revolution been adapted into other media?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The content of Kirarin Revolution is Kirarin Revolution.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5598_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could Kirarin Revolution be a television show?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5598_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any popular characters in Kirarin Revolution?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5598_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can one find more information about Kirarin Revolution?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5598_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5598_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5598_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5598_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5598_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5598_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5598_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5598_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5598_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5598_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5598_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have more triples to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis answer reflects that the query about the content of \"Kirarin Revolution\" being correctly stated within the provided documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because the content of Kirarin Revolution has been described as a sh\u014djo manga series by An Nakahara, which covers genres such as Comedy, Drama, Romance, School life, and Shoujo, indicating that it indeed contains different types of content beyond just itself.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}